theclub.com.hk 2014-12-27

# PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT

**_STATEMENT OF PRACTICES_**

**TYPES OF PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED** **FROM OR COMPILED FOR CUSTOMERS** ****

For the purpose of carrying on the Company's businesses, including account registration and management, provision of products and services, marketing and general administration of The Club, you as our customer may be requested to provide personal data such as, but not limited to, the following, without which it may not be possible to satisfy your request: 

                (a) Your name;

                (b) Information relating to services registered with the HKT Group and the PCCW Group;

                   (c) Contact details, including contact name and telephone number or email address;

                (d) Payment details, including credit card and banking information; or 

                   (e) Information for the verification of identity, including identification type and identification number. 

In some instances, you may also be requested to provide certain data that may be used to further improve the Companyâs services and/or better tailor the type of information presented to you. In most cases, this type of data is optional although, where the requested service is a personalised service, or provision of a product is dependent on your providing all requested data, failure to provide the requested data may prevent the Company from providing the service to you. This type of data may sometimes include, but is not limited to: 

                (a) Your age; 

                (b) Gender; 

                (c) Salary range and employment details; 

                (d) Education and Profession; 

                (e) Hobbies and leisure activities; 

                (f) Other related products and services subscribed to; and 

                (g) Family and household demographics. 

In support of the telecommunications and other services offered by the Company, information may be automatically collected relating to those services so the Company may perform accurate reporting and administration of your accounts such as, but not limited to, call/connection time, duration, origin, and destination. 

The Company's web servers may also collect data relating to your online session, the use of which is to provide aggregated, anonymous, statistical information so that the Company may better meet the demands and expectations of visitors to its sites, and take necessary actions in respect of any illegal or unlawful contents on any website visited through the Companyâs web servers. The types of data may include, but are not limited to:

                (a) The browser type and version; 

                (b) Operating system; 

                (c) The IP address and/or domain name; and

                (d) URLs. 

Some of the Company's web sites may place a "cookie" on your machine; for example to provide personalised services and/or maintain your identity across multiple pages within or across one or more sessions. This information may include, but is not limited to, relevant login and authentication details as well as information relating to your activities and preferences across the Companyâs web sites. 

You can disable cookies on your web browser, however if you do so you may not be able to access all parts of our web sites. 

Occasionally, you may need to provide personal data about other individuals to us (e.g. users whom you have subscribed for services on their behalf). In that event, for the compliance with the Ordinance, you are required to have first obtained the authorization of such individuals before using, disclosing and transferring their personal data, including giving consent on their behalf to our possible use, disclosure and transfer of their personal data, for the purposes you would want to achieve from us. If necessary, we may require you to provide us with any supporting document as may be necessary to prove such authorization. You should also advise them that we can be contacted for further information (please refer to the section titled "The Companyâs Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance Contact Details" for our contact details).

Under certain circumstances, telephone calls made to and from the Companyâs order and/or service hotlines and/or inquiry telephone numbers will be recorded for the purposes of quality control, appraisal, as well as staff management and development. Unless expressly indicated otherwise at the time of calling, such recordings are NOT personal data of the caller and therefore, in respect of the caller, are not subject to the various provisions of the Ordinance and the caller has no rights and/or claims either statutory, contractual or tortious, over or to such data. At all times, care is taken to protect such recordings from inadvertent and/or unauthorized access. 

Any personal data supplied by you will be retained by the Company and will be accessible by our employees and third parties (as applicable) for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy Statement or as otherwise indicated to you. 

**USE OF PERSONAL DATA**

Your personal data may be used for: 

### -          verifying your identity;

### -          processing of your application for our services and loyalty programs;

### -          provision of goods, services and loyalty programs to you;

### -          administration and management of those goods, services and loyalty programs which you have subscribed to;

### -          matching (as defined in the Ordinance) your personal data with other data collected for other purposes and from other sources including third parties in relation to the provision of goods, services and loyalty programs to you;

### -          marketing and advertising of any goods, services and/or loyalty programs to you by the Company, or upon your prescribed consent by related companies, agents, contractors and third party suppliers in accordance with the prevailing requirements in the Ordinance;

### -          business planning and improving goods, services and/or loyalty programs which may be performed by various means including without limitation research, analyses and/or surveys;

### -          processing of any benefits in connection with the supply of goods and services to you;

### -          analysing, verifying, enforcing contractual rights, and/or checking of your credit, payment and/or status in relation to supply of goods and services to you;

### -          processing of any payment instructions, direct debit facilities and/or credit facilities in relation to supply of goods and services to you;

### -          enabling the daily operation of your account and/or the collection of amounts outstanding in your account with the Company including the use of debt collection agents;

### -          enabling the Company to comply with any legal obligations;

### -          maintaining and developing our business systems and infrastructure, including testing and upgrading of these systems;

### -          keeping you informed about goods and services made available by the HKT Group and the PCCW Group and information concerning products and services offered by business partners of the Company;

### -          prevention, detection or investigation of crime; 

-          disclosure as permitted or required by law; and/or

### -          any other purposes as may be agreed to between you and the Company, including the purposes set out in any application or terms and conditions for the supply of specific goods and services.

**ACCURACY OF PERSONAL DATA**

Where possible, the Company will validate data provided using generally accepted practices and guidelines. This includes the use of check sum verification on some numeric fields such as account numbers or credit card numbers. In some instances, the data provided will be validated against pre-existing data held by the Company. In some cases, as per the requirements of the Ordinance, the Company is required to see original documentation before the personal data may be used, such as with Personal Identifiers and/or proof of address. For the purpose of ensuring accuracy or authenticity of the identity document supplied to us, we expect customer to produce customerâs identity document in person for checking at a time convenient to customer. Customer may call our Customer Service Hotline for the necessary arrangement.

The Company fully complies with the "Rights of Access and Correction" obligations of the Ordinance. Please refer to the section titled "Access and Correction of Personal Data" below for details on how you can obtain and correct any personal data relating to you that the Company may hold.

Please note that the accuracy of such personal data we collect, use and disclose depends to a large extent on the information you provide. You have a right to request correction of your personal data and we recommend that you: 

-          let us know if there are any errors in your personal data; and

-          keep us up-to-date with changes to your personal data such as your name or address.

**RETENTION OF PERSONAL DATA**

The Company will destroy any personal data it may hold in accordance with its internal policy. Generally speaking, the Companyâs policies cover the following principles: 

                  (a) personal data will only be retained for as long as is necessary to fulfil the original or directly related purposes for which it was collected, unless the personal data is also retained to satisfy any applicable statutory or contractual obligations; and 

(b) personal data are purged from the Company's electronic, manual, and other filing systems based on the above criteria and the Company's internal procedures. 

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL DATA**

All personal data held by the Company will be kept confidential but the Company may, where such disclosure is necessary to satisfy the purpose, or a directly related purpose, for which the data was collected provide such information to the following parties: 

                (a) any subsidiaries, holding companies, associated companies, or affiliates of, or companies controlled by, or under common control with the Company; 

                (b) any person or company who is acting for or on behalf of the Company, or jointly with the Company, in respect of the purpose or a directly related purpose for which the data was provided; 

                (c) any other person or company who is under a duty of confidentiality to the Company and has undertaken to keep such information confidential, provided such person or company has a legitimate right to such information;

                (d) the Companyâs dealers, agents, contractors, suppliers and other telecommunication, information service providers and content providers; its professional advisers, including its accountants, auditors and lawyers;

                (e) government and regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies and other organisations, as required or authorised by law; 

                (f) any financial institutions, charge or credit card issuing companies, credit providers, credit information or reference bureaux, or collection agencies, security agencies, necessary to establish and support the payment of any services being requested;

                (g) your authorized representatives or your legal advisers when requested by you to do so;

                (h) telecommunications network operators;

                (i) banks, hotels, insurance companies, billing agents and various business partners for reward redemption purposes and benefits as applicable to members of our loyalty programs, including without limitation for purposes of registering members for loyalty program related events;

                (j) organisations who manage our business and corporate strategies (and for such purposes), including those involved in a transfer/sale of all or part of our assets or business (including accounts and trade receivables) and those involved in managing our corporate risk and funding functions (e.g. securitisation); and

                (k) any proposed or actual participant, assignee or transferee of all or any part of the Company's operation or business. 

Personal data may also be disclosed to any person or persons pursuant to any statutory or contractual obligations or as required by court of law, provided such person or persons are able to prove the required right/authority to access such information. In addition, personal data may be disclosed under any of the circumstances described in Part VIII of the Ordinance in which the concerned personal data are exempt from the provisions of Data Protection Principle 3 of the Ordinance. 

**TRANSFER OF PERSONAL DATA OUTSIDE HONG KONG**

At times it may be necessary and/or prudent for the Company to transfer certain personal data to places outside the Hong Kong SAR in order to carry out the purposes, or directly related purposes, for which the personal data were collected. Where such a transfer is performed, it will be done in compliance with the prevailing requirements of the Ordinance. 

**SECURITY OF PERSONAL DATA**

Physical records containing personal data are securely stored in controlled areas when not in use.

Computer data are stored on computer systems and storage media to which access is strictly controlled and/or are located within restricted areas. 

Access to records and data without appropriate management authorization are strictly prohibited. Authorizations are granted only on a "need to know" basis that is commensurate with an individual's Company responsibilities and their training. 

Where the Company holds, uses and/or transmits the Customersâ personal data it will be adequately protected from accidental and/or unauthorized disclosure, change and/or destruction.

You should be aware that no system is impenetrable and no information provided over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us or receive from us over the Internet.

**LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

Our websites ([www.theclub.com.hk](http://www.theclub.com.hk/)) and mobile app may contain links to other sites and pages which are operated by third parties. We have no control over the content of the linked websites or the way in which the operators of those websites deal with your personal data. You should review the privacy policy for those third party websites to understand the ways in which your personal data may be used by those third parties.

**ACCESS AND CORRECTION OF PERSONAL DATA**

Under the Ordinance, individuals have the right to: 

                (a) ascertain whether the Company holds any personal data relating to them and, if so, obtain copies of such data ("right of access"); 

                (b) require the Company to correct personal data in its possession which is inaccurate for the purpose for which it is being used by means of a data access request (right of correction); and 

                (c) ascertain the Company's policies and practices in relation to personal data, which are those policies and practices set out in their entirety herein. 

An individual may exercise his or her right of access by: 

                (a) completing the "Data Access Request Form" as prescribed by the Privacy Commissioner for Personal Data or the "Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance - Data Access Request Form" - see "Note 1" below; 

                (b) sending the completed form, along with appropriate proof of identity (a copy of the applicant's Hong Kong Identity Card or Passport) and the prescribed fee to the Company's Privacy Compliance Officer at the address listed below; 

                (c) alternatively, if you do not wish to provide a copy of your proof of identity, you may present the completed form - see "Note 1" below - in person, along with appropriate identification, at any of the conveniently located Customer Service Centers. There, staff will verify your identity and stamp the completed form appropriately. Please send the stamped form and processing fee to Privacy Compliance Officer (Group Legal Office) at the address listed below for processing. 

The Company will, upon satisfying itself of the authenticity and validity of the access request, make every endeavour to comply with and respond to the request within the period set by the Ordinance (i. e. within 40 days after receiving the request). 

An individual may exercise their right of correction by writing to the Company's Privacy Compliance Officer at the address listed below, specifying the data obtained through the Data Access Request mentioned above which needs to be corrected. 

Satisfactory proof and/or explanation of the inaccuracy is essential before the Company would consider correcting the specified data. 

Upon satisfying itself of the authenticity and validity of the correction request, the Company will comply with and respond to the request as required by the Ordinance. 

**DIRECT MARKETING**

In accordance with the requirements of the Ordinance, the Company will honour a customer's request not to use his or her personal data for the purposes of direct marketing. 

Upon customerâs consent, the Company may use his or her personal data (including name, contact information, and information about the products, services, or loyalty programs that he or she has purchased or subscribed to) and geographical data to deliver to customer, through various communication channels by using email address, correspondence address, mobile phone number, telephone number, service number and service account number, etc., various promotion materials including the Companyâs latest offers, gifts, discounts, benefits, information relating to telecommunications network services (all services or products operating or can be operated on HKTâs telecommunications network such as TV, mobile voice, SMS and data communications, IDD/roaming, Internet connectivity, cloud services, entertainment and data communications on Internet), computer peripheral, accessories and software (including notebooks, handsets, mobile devices and accessories, keyboards, security installations and mobile applications), secretarial services, personal assistance services and information services. Customer may also be provided with the latest offers on various kinds of products or services including gaming, sports, music, beauty products, electronics, technology, e-commerce, cloud services, mobile payment, travelling, banking, investment, entertainment, transportation, household, fashion, food and beverages, alcohol and tobacco, insurance, education, health and wellness, social networking, media and high-end consumer products and services.

Customer can at any time send request to our Privacy Compliance Officer together with registered name and service account number, registered service number or login name, to stop receiving the promotion materials aforesaid or to start receiving the same (if customers have unsubscribed from receiving such materials before). 

Any such request should clearly state the details of the personal data in respect of which the request is being made. Specifically, it is requested that you include the corresponding Company assigned account numbers which are printed on the Company's statements/invoices. 

**THE COMPANY'S PERSONAL DATA (PRIVACY) ORDINANCE CONTACT DETAILS**

All enquiries and requests regarding the Company's compliance with its obligations under the Ordinance should be in writing to The Club, PO Box 9869, GPO Box, Hong Kong.

**Note 1** : 

The Company will handle requests made either on its own form, "Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance - Data Access Request Form" ( _PCO-TEM-01_ ), or on that prescribed by the Hong Kong SAR Privacy Commissioner for Personal Data ([Form OPS003 [revised 09/2012]](http://www.pcpd.org.hk/english/publications/files/Dforme.pdf)), provided all mandatory data as specified in the relevant form has been supplied.

(This Privacy Policy Statement may be amended from time to time and all handling of personal data will be governed by the most recent version of this Privacy Policy Statement, available on our website at [www.hkt.com](http://www.hkt.com/). Â If there is any inconsistency or conflict between the English and Chinese versions, the English version shall prevail.)
